Welcome to Close Enough Floor Where i [Kilian] Tell Backstories that might not be Entirely correct but. They are
Close Enough
[Today] [I] will be Explaining
Dark Souls to Spec Story I will be Referencing Dark Souls 1 and you Can Watch my recap right here [Fellow] [Named] [Vendrick] want to
Start A Kingdom and There was Lots of unused Land Around but he Said now Let's Bulldoze Another Kingdom if They Thought
Was a good place to start a nation We might - so he Obliterated another Kingdom by actually Reading Patch Notes Then Builds his Own
Kingdom on Top of the Previous Inhabitants Corpses The King's Brother
[was] [naval] scientists Inside the Stay in His House all day and do
Experiments for Example Making inanimate Objects Come to life much like a dark souls Player and Someone Saying hey you know
What's better Skyrim A woman Showed up to [vendrick's] [court] She?
Was a Queen from a faraway land now She Didn't Have Any Proof and her Story Had About 17
Holes but She
Was very hot so the [king] Decide to trust her The one Guy?
Objected and he got exiled on the other Side to see a Country Inhabited by giant is going to attack any day now
They will be Here in Two [Days]
You Wake up Tomorrow and Boom [Giants] everywhere what you speak [up] is True I have Decided to Upgrade the fences and
Renew my car insurance Honey Never Heard of
Pre-emptive Strikes Let Me Tell you about a man called george, W Bush when She conveyed them and Didn't find any WMDs but he
Did Kidnap some giants and Brought them back Back Home the undead Curse has Started Spread Throughout The Land and [Vendrick] got infected
Listen Brother I'm going to give you [75%] of the Kingdom's, well Done all These giants to find a cure
Did you find a cure what are you talking about
Alright that now [mate] Spent About 50 Minutes on it then gave up then
I spent the rest of The Budget on A giant Dragon the brother
Also Tortured The giants and giants Can Feel what other giants Feel so back Home in giant Land they had a pretty Hard Time
Concentrating on Office Work so the giants Decided to invade the Kingdom
We've Been Besieging the humans for 120 Years?
[10] More
We get a record I deserve this one
[Hijacking] The Humans Are Destroying Us and they will be here in the Second now what how We Prepared for everything they Could Throw at
Us i bought a lifetime Subscription to [Nord] [on] [I] saw independence day
Travel, oh come on giants are Dead the Country is [Completely] Destroyed and everything is just All-Around Shitty [Hendrick] Is Stressed and Depressed
When did This downfall start Wait a minute hey Honey are you as
Powerful Demon Thing and Trying to Cast World Into Darkness what
No but I do need the first Flames that I know you have okay sure I'm Just going to go out and get A Newspaper
Thanks for Joining Me Here in my Tomb [I] think my wife might [be] Pure Evil
Oh women no I mean Literally She's Trying to Take the Creator of Life that
We for some Reason have in our Basement you have no idea of our Castle smart value [for]?
Women but I made some arrangement to stop her She Needs this ring and I'm going to put it here by my Side and then
You are going to stand Outside of my Tomb and Watch it for the rest of Eternity
For the Rest of Eternity if You know it Can ruin Anymore Can I have your Crown
Chip Sure your friend, Is tiny I thought he, was your friend wait who was that?
Lucky Chick you stole my Crown several Years Later a bearer of the undead Curse
Realizes that he can't die so he downs Three Bottles of Tequila
then Wakes Up two Weeks Later in [Bendrix] Kingdom Unable to remember his entire life you are that Person
Like Check out my Parody subscribing all that Shit I haven't Had Internet for A fucking week I
Haven't Even Picked the Game haven't even Started on a recap yet so i'm Open for Suggestions